最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
原创翻译  双语字幕
你看他  我心都要碎了
Look at him. Breaks my heart.
翻译      睡了午觉赛太公
可怜的小家伙  形单影只
Poor little guy, all alone.
他哥哥为什么不能跟他坐在一起
I don't see why his brother can't sit with him.
校对      表面兄弟赛太公   塑料姐妹YY猫
拜托  玛丽
Come on, Mary.
你上高中时
When you were in high school,
难道你会跟一个9岁小孩吃午饭吗
would you have lunch with a nine-year-old?
我当然会啊
Yes, I would've.
时间轴    风吹来的那片云
那你肯定是哪里有毛病
Well, there's something wrong with you.
我要去陪他
I'm gonna keep him company.
别  别  玛丽  玛丽
Hey, hey, hey, Mary. Mary.
你可得想清楚  现在大家只是无视他
Think this through. Right now the kids are just ignoring Sheldon.
后期      灰灰是菇凉
如果再发现他吃午饭还要妈妈陪会怎么样
What happens if he's sitting with his mommy?
他们说不定会以为我是高三学姐啊
They could mistake me for a senior.
总监     新浪微博@赛太公
我看起来是比你年轻啊
Well, I look younger than you.
先静观其变  好吗
Just give this time, all right?
船到桥头自然直
It'll work itself out.
我母亲从未理解
My mother never understood
我其实很享受独自一人
that I actually enjoyed being alone.
独处让我能思考更重大的事情
Solitude allowed me to think about important things,
比如当你接近事件视界时
like the effect of gravitational forces
地心引力会造成的影响
as you approach an event horizon,
而不是那些无关紧要的事
as opposed to less important things,
比如我哥嘴里一次能塞多少葡萄
like how many grapes my brother can fit in his mouth.
14颗
14!
太厉害啦
Yeah!
哲学家让-保罗·萨特说过
Jean-Paul Sartre said,
"他人即地狱"
"Hell is other people."
这话很有趣  因为这是真的
That's humorous because it's true.
♪ 世上没人比我强壮 ♪
♪ Nobody else is stronger than I am ♪
♪ 昨天我移了一座山 ♪
♪ Yesterday I moved a mountain ♪
♪ 我相信我能当你的英雄 ♪
♪ I bet I could be your hero ♪
♪ 我是个了不起的小家伙 ♪
♪ I am a mighty little man ♪
少
年
谢尔顿
怎么了吗
Something wrong?
为什么谢尔顿数学那么好  我数学却那么差
How come math is easy for Sheldon and hard for me?
我也不知道啊  亲爱的
I don't know, honey,
但你也有你的天赋啊
but you have your own gifts.
比如什么
Like what?
比如说...
Well, like...
你有一头秀丽长发
...you have very pretty hair.
的确
True.
小乔治
Georgie.
能麻烦你帮我一个小忙吗
Would you do me a little tiny favor?
什么事
Like what?
明天午餐时间  你能不能跟你弟弟坐一起吃
Tomorrow at lunch, would you mind sitting with your brother?
千万别  小乔治
Don't do it, Georgie.
你别多管闲事
You stay out of this.
二年级的时候我跟他一起吃过饭
I ate with him in second grade.
导致我的校园关系严重受创
It really hurt my social life.
抱歉了  老妈  没办法
Sorry, Mom. Can't do it.
你为什么这么皮
Why are you such a brat?
可能我渴求关爱呢
Maybe I'm crying for attention.
小姑娘  这事你别闹
This isn't a joke, young lady.
没错  你弟弟是很聪明
Yes, your brother may be smart,
但他在这世上还没有一个朋友
but he doesn't have a friend in the world.
对不起  但我真的很担心他
And I am sorry, but I am very worried about him.
不错啊  你害妈妈快急疯了
Nice going. You're making Mom a nervous wreck.
我干嘛了
What did I do?
你没有朋友  她着急坏了
You don't have any friends, and she is beside herself.
但我不介意没朋友啊
But I'm fine without friends.
我不知道该跟你怎么说了  谢尔顿
I don't know what to tell you, Sheldon.
但她觉得是你的问题
She said it's your fault.
我要去看电视剧了
I'm going to watch ALF.
科学事实
Science fact:
姐妹最差劲了
sisters are the worst.
当你只有90公分高却在高中就读时
When you're three foot ten and in high school,
从A点到B点
getting from point "A" to point "B"
可以是一种要人命的体验
can be a harrowing experience.
但如果"B"点是...
But it's worth it when point "B" is...
图书馆  那就值了
...the library.
信息高速公路的起源地
Home to the original information superhighway,
杜威十进制图书分类法
the Dewey Decimal System.
由美国图书馆专家麦尔威·杜威发明
对世界图书馆分类学有相当大的影响
你好啊  谢尔顿
Hey there, Sheldon.
今天你想看什么书
What can I get for you today?
化学
Chemistry?
量子力学  天文学
Quantum mechanics? Astronomy?
不  今天不看有趣的书
No, nothing fun today.
我想学习怎么交朋友
I need to learn how to make a friend.
亲爱的  适应高中生活碰到困难了吗
Aw, honey, you having a hard time adjusting to high school?
我是对适应地球生活碰到了困难
I'm having a hard time adjusting to Earth.
是啊  我们同病相怜
Yeah. You and me both.
试试这本
Try this.
这书有些上年头了  但还是挺受欢迎的
It's been around a while, but it's still quite popular.
不像我
Unlike me,
只是单纯地上年头
who's just been around a while.
《如何赢取友谊与影响他人》
"How to Win Friends and Influence People."
由戴尔·卡耐基在1936年所写  世上最畅销励志书之一
这本或许有用
This might do it.
原则一
Principle one.
"不要批评  谴责  或抱怨"
"Don't criticize, condemn or complain."
这是我的三大扎心之箭
The three sharpest arrows in my quiver.
我也从此展开了我幼年时期最大的挑战
Thus began the greatest challenge of my young life.
你好啊  乔治
Hello, George.
怎么了
What?
我很欣赏你的一头浓密头发
I do admire your thick head of hair...
乔治
George.
谢谢
Thanks.
这是在干嘛
What's going on?
我在练习运用这本书里教的原则
Well, I'm practicing the principles in this book.
-为什么  -我知道妈妈很担心
- Why? - Well, I know Mom is concerned
我身边没有朋友
that I don't have any friends,
所以我下决心要解决这个问题
so I'm determined to remedy the situation.
乔治
George.
那挺好
Well, good for you.
我这么喊你名字  你有感到受称赞吗  乔治
Do you feel complimented when I say your name, George?
书上说你会有这感受  乔治
The book says you should. George.
大概吧
I suppose.
不过你有点用力过猛
Kind of overdoing it a little.
-谢尔顿  -谢谢你的批评
- Sheldon. - Well, thank you for your criticism.
书里也说  我应该对你任何的进步做出赞赏
It also says I should praise any improvements that you've made.
好吧
Okay.
回头再聊吧
I'll get back to you.
乔治
George.
紧接在这大获成功的测试后
On the heels of that successful beta test,
我决定对我同龄人练习卡耐基原则
I decided to practice the Carnegie principles on someone my own age.
-你好啊  比利·斯巴克斯  -你好啊  谢尔顿
- Hello, Billy Sparks. - Hey, Sheldon.
我真心想多了解你
I am genuinely interested in you
也想鼓励你多聊聊你自己
and would like to encourage you to talk about yourself.
比利·斯巴克斯
Billy Sparks.
谢谢
Thank you.
现在该你说了
You have the floor.
谢谢
Thank you.
现在回想起来 当初我真应该
Looking back, I would've had better luck
去结交那些母鸡
making friends with the chickens.
狼队加油
Go Wolves.
什么
What?
你是拉拉队员  当我说
You're a cheerleader, and by saying
"狼队加油"  我就开始了一段
"Go Wolves," I'm initiating a conversation
你会感兴趣的交谈
about something that interests you.
你是"特殊教育"班的孩子吗
Oh, are you one of those special ed kids?
我妈说我很特殊
My mom says I'm special.
你想跟我做朋友吗
Would you like to be friends?
没什么兴趣
I don't think so.
你确定吗  那如果我告诉你
Are you sure? What if I told you
我很欣赏你着色大胆的浓妆呢
I admired your boldly-applied makeup?
从一号隔间向你们问好
Greetings from stall number one.
虽然我十分讨厌你们气味特殊的"烟"
As much as I detest that odd-smelling cigarette,
但我为你们违反规矩的勇气鼓掌
I do applaud your rule-breaking bravado.
我叫谢尔顿  你们叫什么
My name is Sheldon. What's yours?
男士们好
Hello, gentlemen.
你们上周末有看任何体育节目吗
Did you watch any sports programs over the weekend?
又或者跟姑娘们玩亲亲了吗
Or perhaps did some kissing with girls?
你们能听见我说话吗
Can you hear me?
95  96  97
95, 96, 97.
98.
99  100
99, 100.
你中间数漏了11个数
You missed 11 numbers.
我不需要数学那么好  人家有一头秀发
I don't need to be good at math. I have beautiful hair.
这是我这辈子听过最悲催的话
That's the saddest thing I've ever heard.
你不是已经读完那本书了吗
Didn't you already read that book?
我在重读
I'm reading it again.
为什么
How come?
我肯定有哪里读漏了
I clearly missed something.
我找不到一个愿意跟我当朋友的人
I couldn't find one person who wanted to be my friend.
你看过里面的借书卡了吗
Did you look at the card inside?
为什么
Why?
卡上只有其他借过这本书的人的名字
That's just other people who checked out the book.
这是其他像你一样找不到朋友的废柴名单
It's a list of losers like you who can't find a friend.
那又如何
So?
他们求友心切  而你手握名单
So they're desperate, and you have their names.
太聪明了
That's brilliant.
那你怎么就数不好数呢
Now, how is it that you can't count?
你爸爸跟我说你最近新读了本书
So your father tells me you've been reading a new book?
是啊  是教你怎么交朋友
I am. It's about how to make friends.
你对这件事有兴趣吗
Is that something you're interested in?
没什么兴趣  但米希跟我说
Not really, but Missy told me
我没有朋友你很难过
it makes you sad that I don't have any.
我得去把这姑娘的嘴缝起来
I got to sew that girl's mouth shut.
那发展如何
So how's it going?
书里教的原则对我根本不管用
Well, the principles in the book didn't work for me at all.
不过老爸挺喜欢被人反复叫乔治
Although Dad does like being called George over and over again,
你可以试试这招
so you might give that a try.
宝贝  你不需要因为我而给自己添麻烦
Baby, you don't have to go to any trouble for me.
但我喜欢为你付出
But I like doing things for you.
你是个好人
You're a nice lady.
-但如果那书没用...  -的确没用
- But if the book's not working... - It isn't.
但我意识到如果我去找
But I realized if I find the other people
其他借过这书的人  因为他们也想结交朋友
who checked out the book, they'd be looking for friends, too.
这招真聪明
That's really smart.
-是米希想出来的  -不是吧
- Missy thought of it. - You're kidding.
我当时也像你一样惊讶
I'm as surprised as you are.
打扰一下  英格拉姆女士
Excuse me, Ms. Ingram?
谢尔顿  现在是下课时间
Sheldon, it's recess.
去外面玩  体验一下外面
Go outside, see what it's like.
你是伊芙琳·英格拉姆吗
Are you by any chance Evelyn Ingram?
是的
Yes.
借出过这本书的伊芙琳·英格拉姆吗
The same Evelyn Ingram who checked out this book?
这关你什么事呢
And why is that your business?
我只是在想你当时想要结交朋友
I just assumed you were looking to make a friend.
这是很久以前了
Well, that was a long time ago.
我当时刚从一段惨痛的感情抽身
I had just gotten out of a very difficult relationship.
-跟朋友吗  -朋友
- With a friend? - Friend.
我给那男人奉献了我三年的人生时光
Ha! I gave that man three years of my life
还有我的童真
and my innocence.
我不懂那是什么意思
I don't know what that means.
男人都是骗人的狗东西  只对一件事感兴趣
It means men are lying dogs only interested in one thing.
字典上不是这么解释的
Well, that's not the dictionary definition.
开始都是一样的
Always starts the same.
茫茫人海中的一次对视  不经意地手搭肩上
A quick glance across the room, a casual hand on the shoulder,
在连锁便利店里吃午饭
lunch at Stuckey's.
一开始都是很浪漫  花前月下
Oh, yeah, it's all romance and flowers in the beginning...
这名单被证明是一把双刃剑
The list proved to be a double-edged sword.
原来1936年写的励志书
It turns out self-help books written in 1936
是专门写成给成年人看的
were only of interest to adults.
我就说"老娘是因为在乎才来
You're like, "I'm here because I care.
还有  你的电话也是能打出去的好吗"
And by the way, your phone could make calls, too."
然后他就试着把整件事
Then tries to turn this whole thing around
转移成是你太粘人
like it's all about you being needy,
你当然会说"废话  我当然有需求
and you're like, "Yes, I have needs!
人就是有需求才会是人啊"
That's what makes me human!"
感情上有问题的成人
Emotionally troubled adults.
孩子  出去外面玩吧
Child, go outside.
是的  那是我的签名  你问这个干嘛
Yes, that's my signature. Why do you ask?
我在寻找想交朋友的人
I'm seeking people who want to make friends.
我没兴趣交朋友
I wasn't interested in friends.
我借那本书是为了帮助自己爬到校长位置
I took out that book to help me become school principal.
-成功了吗  -我们现在是在校长办公室说话吗
- Did it work? - Are we sitting in the principal's office?
-不是  -你知道为什么吗
- No. - And you know why?
因为维多利亚·马克艾罗伊不是男人
Because Victoria MacElroy is not a man!
我确认一下  你没兴趣交朋友
So to be clear, you're not interested in making friends?
我唯一有兴趣的就是命够长
What I'm interested in is in living long enough
长到可以看到女人不再被当二等公民对待
to see women no longer treated like second-class citizens.
如果你想长命百岁
Well if your goal is a long life,
那你吃这个热辣芝士堡只能帮倒忙
that chili cheeseburger is a step in the wrong direction.
食物是老娘唯一的慰藉了
Food is all I have.
如同我说的
Like I said,
感情上有问题的成人
emotionally troubled adults.
你要看着我吃饭吗
You gonna watch me eat?
出去
Get out of here.
所有人都告诉我
Everybody told me,
"休伯特  别跟同事约会"
"Hubert, don't date someone from work."
我听话了吗  没有
But did I listen? No.
让我告诉你一件事
Let me tell you something.
她喜欢说我偷走她童真对吗
She likes to say I stole her innocence?
那我的童真呢
Well, what about my innocence?
分手之后我再也不是从前那个我了
I was never the same after we broke up.
两年后
Two years later,
吉文斯先生变成了校长
Mr. Givens became the high school principal,
或许马克艾罗伊女士变成重度胖子也与此有关
which might be why Ms. MacElroy became morbidly obese.
我有头脑  又讨人喜欢  而且我不想炫耀
I had the brains, I had the charm, and I don't like to brag,
但我当年也算得上小鲜肉一枚
but I was pretty easy on the eyes back then.
那娘们简直赚大发了好吗
That woman got herself one heck of a package.
但某些人就是不想被满足
But some people don't want to be satisfied.
这书有用吗
Is that any good?
很遗憾并没有
I'm afraid not.
我没交到一个朋友
I failed to make a single friend.
真可惜  我交朋友也四处碰壁
That sucks. I have a tough time making friends, too.
最糟糕的部分是  我妈妈很在意这件事
The worst part is, it was important to my mom.
我父母也总是给我压力让我去交朋友
My parents pressure me about making friends all the time.
所以你很能理解我的遭遇
So you understand what I'm going through.
我读过那本书  很赞
Oh, I read that book. It's excellent.
罗伯特·戈达德  美国教授  物理学家和发明家
液体火箭的发明者
你也对火箭学有兴趣吗
Are you into rocketry?
我是从气压式喷水火箭开始玩
I started with water propulsion,
后来开始玩固体燃料火箭
worked my way up to solid fuel,
把我家车库烧了之后  我又回去玩喷水火箭了
then went back to water after I set our garage on fire.
-厉害  -我也尝试过去弄铀
- Nice. - I also tried to get some uranium
来做一个原子能引擎  但那东西太难弄到手
and build an atomic engine, but that stuff's hard to find.
这样也好
Probably for the best.
祝你找朋友的道路能一切顺遂
Well, good luck on your quest to find a friend.
你也是
You, too.
如果你还没找到朋友  我有个好消息
If you haven't found one yet, I have good news.
妈  你对百忧解这种药了解吗
Mom, what do you know about the drug Prozac?
了解不多
Not much.
好像能让忧郁的人们开心点  怎么了
Supposed to make people happier. Why?
我只是在想这药或许能帮助我一些老师
I was just thinking some of my teachers might benefit from it.
说到这个
Speaking of which,
有一件你会高兴的事  我今天交到朋友了
you'll be happy to know I made a friend today.
那太好啦
Well, that's nice.
但就像我说过的  交朋友不是为了我
But, as I said, this isn't for me.
是为了你自己
It's for you.
他交到朋友啦
He made a friend!
他成功了
He did it!
我们的儿子交到朋友了
Our little boy has got a friend.
-谁啊  -无所谓啦
- Who is it? - Who cares?
反正是个人类  是个有血有肉的人
It's a human being. It's a warm body.
妈
Mom?
怎么啦  亲爱的
Yes, honey?
我能进来吗  当然
Can I come in? Of course.
冷静
Be cool.
怎么啦  小宝贝
What's up, sweetie?
我想知道我什么时候能继续我火箭学的爱好
I was wondering when I could continue my rocketry hobby.
谢尔顿  我们聊过这个了
Uh, Sheldon, we've been through this.
火箭随便造  但不许发射
You can build them. You just can't launch them.
但发射才是好玩的那部分啊
But launching them is the fun part.
你去跟那被火烧死的松鼠一家解释去
Tell that to the family of squirrels who died in the fire.
好吧
Okay.
我只是想可以跟新朋友一起做这个
It was just something I was hoping to do with my new friend.
等等
Hang on.
行吧
Uh, yes.
做吧
It's fine.
解除禁令
Ban is lifted.
-玛丽  -是为了跟他朋友玩嘛
- Mary... - It's for his friend.
他有朋友了
He's got a friend.
而且当时被烧死的也可能是老鼠啊
Besides, those could have been rats.
被烧得都不成鼠形了  谁知道呢
Their bodies were so badly burned.
我还以为我们要冷静  行吧
I thought we were being cool, but okay.
对了  这样吧
Hey, here's an idea.
要不你邀请你的朋友来家里吃晚饭吧
Why don't you invite your new buddy over for dinner?
-为什么  -亲爱的
- Why? - Well, honey,
因为朋友之间就会这样啊
um, that is what friends do.
我妈妈要我问问你
My mother asked me to ask you
愿不愿意来我们家共进晚餐
if you'd like to join us for dinner.
-为什么  -我还希望你知道为什么呢
- Why? - I was hoping you'd know.
他到了
He's here!
大家保持冷静
Everybody, stay calm!
只是普通的一天  普通的一顿晚餐
Just a normal day, just a normal dinner.
我能去电视前吃吗
Can I eat in front of the TV?
不行  但你可以在谢尔顿朋友的面前吃
No, you can eat in front of Sheldon's friend.
-卧槽  -我知道"卧槽"是什么意思
- Aw, fudge. - I know what "fudge" means,
你差一点点就要挨削了  小姑娘
and you are right on the edge, young lady.
欢迎你来
Welcome.
所以...
So, uh...
丹  你这是哪国名字
Tam. What kind of name is that?
是越南名  先生
Vietnamese. Sir.
懂了  我也曾经在那里待过
Sure. You know, I spent a little time over there.
我在军队
Army.
你妈妈的名字不叫金李吧
Your mom's name isn't Kim-Lee, is it?
不  先生
No. Sir.
太好了
Good.
你懂的  小国家嘛
I mean, you know, it's a small country.
说不定就...
So...
玛丽  还要多久才能做完
Mary, how's that food coming?
快啦
Almost.
越南  就像电影《第一滴血》吗
So, Vietnam, like in Rambo.
该电影男主角兰博是个越战退伍军人
该片的第二部场景是在越南
-是的  -那电影超屌
- Yes. - That's a cool movie.
是啊
Yes.
你有在里面演出吗
Are you in it?
没有
No.
你为什么会觉得你认识他妈妈
Why would you think you knew his mom?
好啦  丹
All right, Tam.
我决定给你做纯正的德州风味晚餐
I decided I was gonna make you a real Texas dinner.
德州烧烤鸡肉与牛胸肉
Barbecued chicken and brisket.
谢谢您
Thank you.
我估计你应该也很烦
Well, I figured you were probably tired
你吃的东西会在盘子上扭动了
of stuff wiggling around on your plate.
我们来饭前祷告
Okay, let's say grace.
丹  当我们说"耶稣"
Now, Tam, when I say "Jesus,"
也欢迎你在你脑海里说"菩萨"
feel free to say the word "Buddha" in your head.
我其实是信天主教的
I'm actually Catholic.
那就太不幸了
Oh. Well, that's too bad.
感谢主  赐予我们桌上的食物
Thank you, God, for this food,
也保佑准备这餐点的人
and bless the hands that prepared it.
也感谢您给谢尔顿带来了新朋友
And thank you so much for Sheldon's new friend.
阿门
Amen.
丹  跟我们聊聊你的家人啊
So, Tam, tell us about your family.
你们为什么会来德克萨斯
What brings y'all to Texas?
在美战结束过后
Well, after the American War...
你是说越战吧
You mean the Vietnam War.
我们那里叫美战
We call it the American War.
然后呢
Hmm. Anyway,
在战争结束后  我父亲被送去再教育营
after the war, my father was sent to a reeducation camp
因为他在战时站错边
because he fought on the wrong side.
错边是指我们这边吧
You mean our side.
礼貌性不说穿而已
I was trying to be nice.
所以有很多年
So, for many years,
我们一家一直都非常穷
my mother and my sisters and I were very poor
吃不饱是常事
and very often didn't have much to eat.
最后当我爸爸被放出来后...
Then, when he was released...
他们在再教育营里都教育他什么了
What'd they teach him at the reeducation camp?
教他如何成为共产党人
How to be a communist.
酷啊  就像电影里那样
Cool, like in Rambo.
当我爸爸被放出来后
When he was released,
我们坐小船出逃
we escaped on a small boat
我们在海上漂了几周  一路躲着柬埔寨海盗
and spent many weeks at sea dodging Cambodian pirates
最终漂到了泰国
until we reached Thailand.
那里好像是个很美的国家
Oh, that's supposed to be a beautiful country.
-很美的阳光沙滩  -我不知道
- Lovely beaches. - I wouldn't know.
我们被逼着住进难民营
We were forced to live in a refugee camp,
我们唯一能吃到的只有鸽子与老鼠
where the only thing we had to eat were pigeons and rats.
这时候就要靠辣酱了
Ha! That's a job for hot sauce.
最后
Finally,
我们被允许来到美国
we were allowed to come to United States
在德州加尔维斯顿重新开始
and start over in Galveston.
我爸爸辛苦存钱  终于买下一艘捕虾船
My father saved money and bought his own shrimp boat.
守得云开见月明  对吧
There's a happy ending. Huh?
孩子们看  当生活困难重重
See, kids? When the going gets tough,
-大美利坚会伸出援手  -的确是
- America provides. - It did.
直到极端白人至上组织烧了我家的船
Until the Ku Klux Klan burned our boat
还把我们赶跑
and chased us away.
要试试说这一段有何美好之处吗
You gonna put a good spin on that one?
所以我们搬来了马德福
So we came to Medford
然后开了一家便利店
and opened up a convenience store.
我父母一天工作16小时
My parents work 16 hours a day,
一周7天都不休息
seven days a week
就为了挣一点微薄的钱
for very little money.
这也太致郁了
Well, that was depressing.
我不明白它为什么不能发射
I don't understand why it didn't launch.
我也不懂
Me, neither.
邪恶的纳粹科学家50年前就能了
Evil Nazi scientists did it 50 years ago.
这能有多难啊
How hard could it be?
有什么事吗
Can I help you?
女士  抱歉打扰了  我们是联邦调查局
Sorry to bother you, ma'am. FBI.
我们想找谢尔顿·李·库珀
We're looking for a Sheldon Lee Cooper.
乔治
George!
我在蹲坑呢
I'm on the can.
现在
Now!
-怎么了  -这两位先生是联邦调查局的
- What? - These gentlemen are with the FBI.
他们想找谢尔顿谈话
They want to talk to Sheldon.
什么
What?
我们...
We... Uh...
你们肯定是哪里误会了
Y-You fellas must have made a mistake.
谢尔顿才9岁
Sheldon's nine.
某个住在这个地址的人
Well, someone living at this address
近期曾试图打给加拿大的矿场
recently called a mining operation in Canada
想要买铀
and tried to buy uranium.
可能真的不是误会
Okay, maybe it's not a mistake.
这不可能啦
It's ridiculous.
我们去问问他吧
Let's just go talk to him.
他就是个一个小小小不点而已
He's just a little, itty-bitty thing.
真的  他人畜无害
Really, he's harmless.
对不起
Sorry!
他在车库里呢
He's in the garage.